<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://yourdomain.com/charity/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://yourdomain.com/charity/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://yourdomain.com/charity/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-01-02T04:18:14-08:00</updated><id>http://yourdomain.com/charity//</id><title type="html">With everyone ALL IN- It’s Easy</title><subtitle>Write your site description here. It will be used as your sites meta description as well!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Help find RAF Serviceman Corrie McKeague</title><link href="http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/09/27/corrie/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Help find RAF Serviceman Corrie McKeague" /><published>2014-09-27T05:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2014-09-27T05:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/09/27/corrie</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/09/27/corrie/">&lt;p&gt;
On Friday 23rd September British Serviceman, RAF Airman Corrie McKeague went for a night out in Bury St Edmunds, with his mates from their nearby RAF Base at Honnington.
Corrie was last seen on CCTV in Bury St Edmunds town centre at 3:25am on Sat 24th September, walking in to a dead-end, loading bay area. Corrie has not been seen since.
The Police investigation team, through a combination of lack of resources, intransigence and incompetence have failed to capture and process vital evidence and still lack the basic resources to efficiently process a tiny number of phone calls per week.
After so many weeks of managing this search, Corrie's Mum, Nicola and his brothers Makeyan and Darroch are now desperately seeking your assistance to allow them to continue the search.

&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/charity/img/post-corrie.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Post Sample Image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;

With your support we would like to use all funds to:
1. Fund the appointment of a Private Investigator.
2. Fund a data analyst to undertake the work the Police are not capable of resourcing. Collect, collate and analyse all of the information gathered so far and that will continue to be collected.
3. Fund the associated costs of offering a reward (this has already been secured).
4. The overhead cost of phone numbers and computer.
5. Cover the additional costs of being away from home for Nicola, Darroch and Makeyan in order to maintain their presence in Bury St Edmunds, from their home in Scotland. The family are committed to keeping these costs low.
We will have an independent accountant manage the record of receipts for all expenditure, which will be available publicly
All donations will be gratefully received and faithfully applied in the continued search for Corrie. When we find Corrie, any remaining funds may be used for Corrie's possible care or will be donated to charities, including local Search team SULSAR.
We desperately need your help to be able to bring Corrie home.
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Dennis Fisher</name></author><summary type="html">On Friday 23rd September British Serviceman, RAF Airman Corrie McKeague went for a night out in Bury St Edmunds, with his mates from their nearby RAF Base at Honnington.
Corrie was last seen on CCTV in Bury St Edmunds town centre at 3:25am on Sat 24th September, walking in to a dead-end, loading bay area. Corrie has not been seen since.
The Police investigation team, through a combination of lack of resources, intransigence and incompetence have failed to capture and process vital evidence and still lack the basic resources to efficiently process a tiny number of phone calls per week.
After so many weeks of managing this search, Corrie's Mum, Nicola and his brothers Makeyan and Darroch are now desperately seeking your assistance to allow them to continue the search.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hire a detective to find Finn the stolen boxer</title><link href="http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/09/24/fin/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hire a detective to find Finn the stolen boxer" /><published>2014-09-24T05:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2014-09-24T05:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/09/24/fin</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/09/24/fin/">&lt;p&gt;
This fund will help to find Finn by hiring a detective to find him ! Please give as I want to help his family to get Finn home where he belongs and to find the people who stole him !
We need to stop this from happening again !
Joy his mum is distraught and needs our help !

&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/charity/img/post-fin.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Post Sample Image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Dennis Fisher</name></author><summary type="html">This fund will help to find Finn by hiring a detective to find him ! Please give as I want to help his family to get Finn home where he belongs and to find the people who stole him !
We need to stop this from happening again !
Joy his mum is distraught and needs our help !</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Support Mia Presch from Great Corby.</title><link href="http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/09/18/i-presch/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Support Mia Presch from Great Corby." /><published>2014-09-18T05:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2014-09-18T05:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/09/18/i-presch</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/09/18/i-presch/">&lt;p&gt;On Thursday 8 th December Mia Presch our 3 year old neighbour was diagnosed with Wilms Tumour, a rare children's Kidney Cancer, which affects only about 70 children a year in the U.K.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have known Mia since she was a baby. She is a clever, adorable, beautiful little girl who likes to visit her neighbours, and has just started Great Corby School nursery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Friday 16th December Mia is starting a four week course of chemotherapy, at the R.V.I in Newcastle, which will be followed by surgery to remove the tumour and one Kidney, and then more chemotherapy, so will involve regular 120 mile round trips to Newcastle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our aim is to raise funds to support Mias parents and her one year old sister Darecy. We would also like to send her small regular treats to brighten her day and help make her stays in hospital more bearable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are well aware that Christmas is approaching and is an expensive time of year, and every family is faced with their own needs, However if people would please consider making a financial donation, no matter how big or small to help support this family during this difficult period, it would be much appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;The Final Frontier&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankyou &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/charity/img/post-presch.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Post Sample Image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Dennis Fisher</name></author><summary type="html">On Thursday 8 th December Mia Presch our 3 year old neighbour was diagnosed with Wilms Tumour, a rare children's Kidney Cancer, which affects only about 70 children a year in the U.K.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Help our friend Jay Clark</title><link href="http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/08/24/clark/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Help our friend Jay Clark" /><published>2014-08-24T05:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2014-08-24T05:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/08/24/clark</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/08/24/clark/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/charity/img/post-clark.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Post Sample Image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want to help our friend Jay Clark who has pancreatic cancer. He was diagnosed in Oct 2015 when he was expecting his first child with his partner Caroline. We were overjoyed for Jay and Caroline that he was here to see his beautiful son Maxie born on Jan 9th 2016. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More devastating news came in Feb 2016. Pancreatic cancer has a very low survival rate and is considered incurable. It had spread to Jay's liver and his doctors could only offer him palliative (end of life) care. Jay was 41. It was heart breaking when Jay broke the news to his close friends. He was so strong and offered comfort to everybody. He only asked for help to look after his son when he was gone. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A month later his doctors decided the cancer hadn’t spread to his liver. His life expectancy was now looking so much better. The diagnosis was still terminal but we could dare to dream that he might see his son’s first Xmas. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jay’s rollercoaster experience continued when his mother died of cancer soon after. How much can anyone be expected to deal with? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jay and Caroline have been inspirational in the way they have dealt with everything and have written about their experience in the BeMoreJay blog: https://www.facebook.com/Bemorejay/ It’s actually written from Maxie’s perspective. (Mummy may be helping!) Maxie occasionally let’s Daddy post too. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a lot of painful treatment Jay found out on Oct 14th that the cancer has spread to his liver. It is beyond doubt now. He is currently on a course of palliative chemotherapy and researching alternative treatments that may produce a miracle. He wants to be here for Maxie’s first Xmas and make it amazing. It’s heartbreaking to write that it may be the only Xmas Jay gets to spend with Maxie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want to raise as much money as possible to help this lovely family. It could be for healthcare expenses, a bucket list, something towards a trust fund for Maxie. It’s for them to do with exactly as they please to make their journey more bearable.
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Dennis Fisher</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Help the victims, families and communities of the Croydon</title><link href="http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/07/08/victims/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Help the victims, families and communities of the Croydon" /><published>2014-07-08T05:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2014-07-08T05:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/07/08/victims</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/07/08/victims/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/charity/img/post-croydon.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Post Sample Image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday 9 November 2016 a tram derailment occurred in Croydon killing seven people, the worst loss of life in tram or train incident in the UK since 2004. Alongside the fatalities, over 50 people suffered injuries when the tram derailed near Sandilands tram stop, some of which were life changing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The disaster has impacted not only on the passengers and their families, but also on the wider community living and working in the surrounding area. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many of those involved will require long-term emotional and financial support in the difficult months ahead. This is the official fund is to raise money to enable those directly affected by this tragedy, their families, and where appropriate, the wider community, to have access to ongoing care and support. &lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Dennis Fisher</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Help Salli pay some of her mortgage</title><link href="http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/06/10/Salli/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Help Salli pay some of her mortgage" /><published>2014-06-10T05:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2014-06-10T05:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/06/10/Salli</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://yourdomain.com/charity/2014/06/10/Salli/">&lt;p&gt;My friend Salli Grant sadly lost both of her children Jackson 17 and Millie 12 in a tragic traffic accident on the A36 near Salisbury on the 10th October this year, in her words &quot;On October 10th my world ended&quot; and if the Loss of her children wasn't bad enough the knock on effect of this unbelievable tragedy is that she has lost income from their loss. Salli is a self employed fitness instructor and runs a company called Happy Hearts providing Cardiac and Pulmonary rehabilitation to over 450 Members at 13 different locations around the Wiltshire, Dorset area. At the moment Salli is so grief stricken and full of overwhelming sadness that she is unable to carry out her role as instructor and as such she has no income and the reality is that within a few weeks she could lose her family home. Myself and Geoff Stokes are helping out with taking some of the classes at the moment but this is probably not a long term sustainable solution to the problem. I am totally indebted to Salli as she has saved mine and many others lives with her drive and enthusiasm for life, personally, for helping me back to Heart fitness and pulling me back from the edge of life after my Heart Attack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/charity/img/post-saili.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Post Saili Image&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My intention is along with other close friends and family and from the Happy Hearts community is to raise enough money over the next few weeks to help her to pay her mortgage for at least a few months until she can get the help and rehabilitation that she needs and perhaps help her to return to helping others at Happy Hearts and keep the only thing she has left............. her house. I am not asking for charity here and am not asking you to donate thousands of pounds any amount would be appreciated, if i and her family and others around her could pay the Mortgage we would but we cant, but i will not stand by and let Salli lose everything if you think you can help in any way please contact me or please donate as much as you can, it will all go to help keep her Childrens home. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Dennis Fisher</name></author><summary type="html">My friend Salli Grant sadly lost both of her children Jackson 17 and Millie 12 in a tragic traffic accident on the A36 near Salisbury on the 10th October this year, in her words &quot;On October 10th my world ended&quot; and if the Loss of her children wasn't bad enough the knock on effect of this unbelievable tragedy is that she has lost income from their loss. Salli is a self employed fitness instructor and runs a company called Happy Hearts providing Cardiac and Pulmonary rehabilitation to over 450 Members at 13 different locations around the Wiltshire, Dorset area. At the moment Salli is so grief stricken and full of overwhelming sadness that she is unable to carry out her role as instructor and as such she has no income and the reality is that within a few weeks she could lose her family home. Myself and Geoff Stokes are helping out with taking some of the classes at the moment but this is probably not a long term sustainable solution to the problem. I am totally indebted to Salli as she has saved mine and many others lives with her drive and enthusiasm for life, personally, for helping me back to Heart fitness and pulling me back from the edge of life after my Heart Attack.</summary></entry></feed>
